localyte.com 2013-11-28

# Localyte.com - Travel like a Local!

## Localyte Privacy Policy [Last updated on June 15, 2010]

#### What This Privacy Policy Covers

This privacy policy covers the use of the Localyte web site at http://www.localyte.com, a service owned and operated by Nile Project, Inc., including how Localyte treats personal information that Localyte collects and receives. Pursuant to Localyte's Terms of Use, you must be 18 years or older to use this site. Therefore, this policy makes no provision for individuals under 18 years old.

#### Information Collection and How it is Used

General Information: 

  * Localyte will not sell or disclose your name or e-mail address to third parties without your explicit consent, except as specified in this privacy policy.
  * Localyte collects personal information when you register to use Localyte services or to post content on Localyte. At registration you are asked for your email address and certain other optional information.
  * Localyte automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookies, and the pages you request.
  * Localyte uses information for the following general purposes: products and services provisioning, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, research, and anonymous reporting. IP addresses are automatically reported by your browser each time you view a web page. Your IP address is stored in Localyte's user registration databases when you register with Localyte. IP addresses may be used for various research purposes.

#### Service-related Announcements

Localyte will send you a welcome/confirmation email when you sign up for Localyte's services. Receipt of this email is required for using Localyte's services.

Localyte will send you service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so.

You may not opt-out of service-related communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account by emailing [support@localyte.com](mailto:support@localyte.com) from the email address you signed up with.

#### Administrative Messages

Localyte may periodically email you with administrative messages. Localyte will not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. Your information may be combined with information Localyte collects from other companies and used to improve and personalize services, content and advertising. If you don't wish to receive administrative messages or participate in these programs, simply opt-out by emailing [support@localyte.com](mailto:support@localyte.com).

#### Choice/Opt-out

If you no longer wish to receive administrative messages, you may opt-out by emailing [support@localyte.com](mailto:support@localyte.com).

#### Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. If you reject all cookies, you will not be able to use Localyte products or services that require you to "sign in," and you may not be able to take full advantage of the Localyte service. Localyte uses its own cookies for a number of purposes, including to: Access your information when you "sign in"; keep track of preferences you specify while you are using Localyte's services; display the most appropriate advertising banners, based on your interests and activity on Localyte; estimate and report Localyte's total audience size and traffic; conduct research to improve Localyte's content and services.

#### Information Sharing and Disclosure

Any information you include in your Localyte profile is accessible to the public on the Localyte.com website and through Localyte.com partner websites and services. Do not post any information on your profile that you do not wish the public to see. Whether or not you have a Localyte profile, when you post a message or review, the entire message or review along with your Localyte ID or alias is visible to other users. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

Localyte will not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with nonaffiliated parties except as specified in this Privacy Policy to provide products or services you have requested or when Localyte has your permission.

Localyte may be required to disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, including without limitation the following:

  * Localyte may disclose personally identifiable information to third parties in compliance with Localyte's Copyright Policy;
  * Localyte may disclose personally identifiable information if, in its sole discretion Localyte believes it is necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, to comply with subpoenas. or in relation to a violation of the Localyte Terms of Use or Privacy Policy. other unlawful activity, or as otherwise required by law.

Localyte may share aggregated demographic information with business partners.

Localyte will transfer information about you if Localyte is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Localyte will notify you by email or by putting a prominent notice on the Localyte web site before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

#### Your Use of Other User's Personal Information

As part of transacting on Localyte, you may obtain another Localyte user's email address, address and/or other information. Pursuant to Localyte's Terms of Use, you have a limited license to use this information. This information should only be used for Localyte-related communications or for Localyte-facilitated transactions. Localyte has not granted you a license to use the information for unsolicited commercial messages. Without limiting the foregoing, without express consent from the user, you are not licensed to add any Localyte user to your email or physical mail list.

#### Forums / Chat Rooms / Profiles / Messages / Reviews

If you use a forum or chat room on this site, or post a profile, message or review, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, and/or used by others to send you unsolicited messages. Localyte is not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums, chat rooms, profile pages, messages or reviews.

#### Third Parties

The service may permit you to link to other websites on the Internet, and other websites may contain links to the our site. In addition, Localyte has partnered with third party businesses to provide certain services to you, which may be integrated into the Localyte service. These other websites and third party service providers are not under our control, and such links do not constitute an endorsement by us of those other websites, the services offered through them, or their privacy practices. The privacy and security practices of websites linked to or from our site are not covered by this Privacy Policy, and Company is not responsible for the privacy or security practices or the content of such websites. We recommend that you carefully review any third party terms of use and privacy policies prior to submitting your personal information to such third party websites.

#### Editing and Deleting Account Information

You can change your Localyte Account Information at any time. Localyte may send you certain communications relating to the Localyte service, such as service-related announcements and administrative messages that are considered part of your Localyte account. You can delete your Localyte account by emailing [support@localyte.com](mailto:support@localyte.com). Please note that your identification, billing and contact information may remain in Localyte's records for some period.

Localyte limits access to personal information about you to employees who Localyte believes reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. Your Localyte Account Information is password-protected.

If your personally identifiable information changes you may correct or update it by making the change on Your Localyte Page. You may delete or deactivate your account by emailing Customer Support at [support@localyte.com](mailto:support@localyte.com) or by postal mail at the contact information listed below. Localyte will respond to your request within 10-20 business days.

#### Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. Localyte follows generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once Localyte receives it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while Localyte strives to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, Localyte cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on Localyte's Web site, you can email Localyte at [support@localyte.com](mailto:support@localyte.com).

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Localyte may amend this Privacy Policy. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes to our privacy policy, we will notify you by email so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed.

#### Questions

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy at Localyte, please email us at [support@localyte.com](mailto:support@localyte.com). Your privacy is important to us and we will make every effort to resolve your concerns.
